We will start this exercise with a 3 -2 -1 method.
Find a comfortable position.
Close your eyes.
Take a deep breath.
And while exhaling, mentally repeat and visualize the number 3
three times.
To help you learn to relax physically at level 3, I'm going
to direct your attention to different parts of your body relax
your scalp relax your forehead relax your eyes and the tissue
surrounding your eyes with a slight smile relax your face and
the muscles in your face relax your throat, externally and
internally.
Relax your shoulders, arms and hands. hands.
Take a deep breath and while exhaling relax your chest
externally and internally. internally.
Take another deep breath and while exhaling relax your abdominal
area externally and internally.
Relax your thighs.
Relax your knees.
relax your calves relax your feet you are now at a deeper
healthier level of mind deeper than than before.
This is your physical relaxation level 3.
Whenever you mentally repeat and visualize the number 3, your
body will relax as completely as you are now and more so
every time you practice.
To enter mental relaxation level 2, take a deep breath and while
exhaling mentally repeat Repeat and visualize the number 2 three
times.
You are now at level 2.
Level 2 is for mental relaxation where noises will not distract
you.
Instead, noises will help you to relax mentally more and more.
to improve mental relaxation at level 2 visualize tranquil and
passive scenes do that now
take another deep breath and while exhaling mentally repeat and
visualize the number one three times you are now at level one
a deeper healthier level of mind, deeper than before.
To help you enter a deeper, healthier level of mind, I'm going
to count from 10 to 1.
On each descending number, you will feel yourself going deeper,
and you will enter a deeper healthier level of mind 10 9
feel going deeper 8 7 6 deeper and deeper five four three
deeper and deeper two one you are now at a deeper healthier
level of mind deeper than before it is a wonderful feeling to
be deeply relaxed a a very healthy state of being.
From now on, I will occasionally be speaking in your place.
Effective sensory projection statements for success.
I am now able to attune my intelligence by developing my sensing
faculties and to experience myself as any point, place level or
depth so as to be aware of any actions taking place I
am able to function in non locality regarding time and space I
am aware that intelligence exists at all levels and depths in
the universe and therefore I can attune to to all information.
I am now able to use my sensing faculties and to experience
myself as any matter kingdom,
mineral, plant, animal, and human if this is what I desire to
do.
I am now able to detect abnormalities whenever such
abnormalities exist within any kingdom any level any depth I am
now able to apply corrective measures and to bring back to
normalcy any abnormality found within any kingdom any level and
any depth quantum energy is available at any level to be acted
upon to create through the subjective and objective dimensions
we will now continue programming effective sensory projection
for your success
and program information with the use of mental projection for
your benefit it we will establish subjective points of reference
by projecting into the animate matter kingdom with reproductive
intelligence into the plant life kingdom becoming aware of
different levels and different depths now at the count of three
you will mentally project yourself to your living room. One,
two, three.
Mentally project yourself to the center of your living room
facing the south wall.
You are now at the center of your living room facing the
south wall.
We will now replay the objective impressions of the leaves and
also establish subjective points of reference at the count of
three we will visualize the first leaf one two three extend your
arm objectively and visualize the first leaf leaf.
Mentally sense the leaf.
Bring it closer and closer to your forehead.
Now touch your forehead and mentally project yourself into the
leaf.
You are now within the first leaf.
You may return your hand to rest on your lap.
At the count of three, test for light, intensity, and color.
One, two, three.
Sense the intensity and color of light within the leaf.
how does light within the leaf compare with the light within
object number one
object number two and object number three
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three, test for temperature, one, two, three. 3.
Sense the temperature within leaf number 1.
How does this compare with the temperature of object number 1,
object number 2,
and object number 3?
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three, test for odour, one, two, three. Sense
the odor within the leaf.
How does this compare with the odor of object number one, object
number two, and object Object number three, whatever you
perceive with your imagination at this dimension, you can use as
a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three, test for solidity of material, one, two,
three, objectively form a fist and knock on the inside of the
leaf.
How does this reflected sound compare with the reflected sound
of object number one,
object number two,
and object number three?
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future at
the count of three touch your forehead to come out of leaf
number one one two three touch your forehead
you are now coming out of the leaf extend your arm and
mentally hold the leaf at arm's length.
Now allow the leaf to float in space using the south wall
of your living room as a background.
Keep the leaf rotating.
You may return your hand to rest on your lap.
At the count of three the color of the wall will change
to red 1 2 3 how does the leaf stand out against
a red background how does this compare with object number one
object number two and object number three keep the leaf
rotating.
At the count of three the color of the wall will change
to green. One, two, three.
How does a leaf stand out against a green background?
And how How does this compare with object number one, object
number two, and object number three? Keep the leaf rotating.
At the count of three, the color of the wall will change
to blue. One, two, three.
How does the leaf stand out against a blue background?
How does this compare with object number one, object number two,
and object number three? Keep the leaf rotating.
The color of the wall will now change back to green, back
to red, back to the actual color of the wall now the
first leaf will disappear from the scene the first leaf has
disappeared from the scene at the count of three we will
visualize the second leaf one two three extend your arm
objectively and visualize the second leaf.
Mentally sense this leaf as you bring it closer and closer
toward your forehead.
Now touch your forehead and mentally project yourself into the
leaf.
You are now within leaf number two.
You may return your hand to rest on your lap at the
count of three test for light intensity and color one two three
sense the intensity and color of light within the second leaf
how does the light within this leaf compare with the light
within the first leaf whatever you perceive with your
imagination at this dimension you can use as a point of
reference in the future at the count of three test for
temperature one two three 3.
Sense the temperature within this leaf.
How does it compare with the temperature within the first leaf?
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
at the count of three test for odor one two three sense
the odor within this same leaf
how does this compare with the odor of the other leaf
whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future at
the count of three tests for solidity of material one two three
3.
Objectively form a fist and knock on the inside of the second
leaf.
How does this sound compare with the sound of the first leaf?
whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future at
the count of three touch your forehead and come out of the
leaf one two three touch your forehead you are now coming out
of the leaf extend your arm and mentally hold the leaf at
arm's length allowing it to float in space against the
background of your south wall keep the leaf rotating you You may
return your hand to rest on your lap.
At the count of three, the color of the wall will change
to red.
One, two, three.
How does the leaf stand out against a red background?
How does this compare with the first leaf?
Keep the second leaf rotating. at the count of three the color
of the wall will change to green one two three
how does the leaf stand out against a green background how does
this compare with the first leaf keep the second leaf rotating
at the count of three the color of the wall will change
to blue one two three how does the leaf stand out against
a blue background.
How does this compare with the first leaf?
Keep the second leaf rotating.
The color of the wall will now change back to green, back
back to red,
back to the actual color of the wall.
The second leaf will now disappear from the scene.
The second leaf has now disappeared.
We will continue programming effective sensory projection for
your success
and to continue programming information with the use of mental
projection for your benefit. We will establish subjective points
of reference in the animate matter kingdom with reproductive
intelligence,
the animal life kingdom, at different levels and depths.
At the count of three, mentally project your pet to the same
level where you had the chair and the leaves.
one two three your pet is facing you notice how your pet
stands out against the natural color of the wall at the count
of three the wall will turn black one two three notice how
your pet stands out against the black screen mentally Turn your
pet to the left.
Turn the pet away from you.
Turn the pet to the right.
Place the pet facing you.
At the count of three, the color of the screen will change
to red, one, two, three. 3.
The screen is now red. Study your pet.
How does a pet stand out against a red background?
At the count of 3, the color of the screen will change
to green. 1, 2, 3.
Study the pet against a green background.
at the count of three the color of the screen will change
to blue one two three
now study the pet against the blue background whatever you
perceive with your imagination at this dimension you can use as
a point of reference in the the future.
The color of your mental screen will now change back to green,
back to red,
back to black.
Now mentally bring your pet closer, close enough to touch,
noticing how how the pet appears to become bigger as it gets
closer.
Now objectively extend your arms and hold the pet by the head,
one hand on each side.
Steady the head from several angles from this outer point of
view.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future
Observe the eyes the nose the ears
the fur or outer covering
Focus your attention on the pet's forehead head at the count of
three we will mentally enter the bone structure level of this
kingdom
one two three we are now at the bone structure level desire
to perceive and imagine a bone or bones bring back a memory
when you have seen a skull study the pet skull from several
angles
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
Focus your attention on the pet's forehead and at the count of
three we will enter the brain cell level. One, two, three.
Desire to perceive and imagine brain cells or brain matter.
Bring back a memory when you have seen a brain in a
picture or or a chart.
Study the brain from several angles.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three, we will go back to the bone
structure level. One, two, three.
now at the count of three we will again be at the
outer level of this kingdom one two three we are now at
the outer level of this kingdom again observe the eyes the nose
the ears the fur or outer covering now mentally move the pet
a little higher and hold it by the rib cage.
Objectively place one hand on either side of the rib cage.
Now focus your attention on the center of the pet's chest.
At the count of three we will enter the bone structure level.
One, two, two, three.
Desire to perceive and imagine the ribs of your pet.
Now the spinal column.
Study the complete skeletal body.
You can raise or lower the skeleton to any position or angle
and it will remain in that position or angle.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
Again, focus your attention on the chest area.
At the count of three, we will enter the heart tissue level,
one, two, three. 3.
Desire to perceive and imagine a heart.
Bring back a memory when you have seen a heart.
Study the heart from several angles.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
Again, focus your attention on the heart.
At the count of three, we will sense the heart transparent.
One, two, three.
Bring back a memory of having seen a picture of a transparent
heart.
Imagine what it would look like.
imagine how it would function whatever you perceive with your
imagination at this dimension you can use as a point of
reference in the future at the count of three we will enter
the lung tissue level one two three desire to perceive and
imagine two lungs bring back a memory when you have seen
pictures of lungs.
Study the lungs of this pet from several angles.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three we will enter the kidney tissue level
1, 2, 3.
Desire to perceive and imagine two kidneys.
Bring back a memory of having having seen kidneys, such as in
anatomy book pictures.
Study your pet's kidneys from several angles.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future. at
the count of three we will enter the liver tissue level one
two three desire to perceive and imagine a liver study your pets
liver from several angles
whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future at
the count of three we will go back to the kidney level
one two three Three.
Now back to the lung level.
Now back to the heart level.
Now back to the skeletal level.
Now to the outer level of this dimension.
Now mentally place your pet against the wall in the area of
your mental screen.
Now mentally turn your pet to your left.
Now turn it away from you.
Now to your right Now towards you
Change the color of the screen to red Change the color of
the screen to green
Now change the color to blue.
We will now change the color of the screen back to green,
back to red, back to black.
Now imagine your pet in perfect health.
Now cause your pet to disappear from the scene.
Your pet has now disappeared from the scene.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as points of reference in the future.
It is now an accomplished fact that subjective points of
reference have been established at different levels and depths
of the animate matter kingdom with reproductive intelligence,
the plant life kingdom, and the animal life kingdom.
To function at these levels and to use these points of
reference,
all you need is a sincere desire to solve problems.
Your mind will automatically seek out these points of reference
where you will perceive and become aware of information that you
can use to solve such problems, and this is so.
Every time you function at these levels of the mind and at
these points of reference, you will receive beneficial effects
physically and mentally.
You may use these levels of the mind and these points of
reference to help yourself, to help your loved ones, and to help
any human being who needs help physically and mentally.
You will always use these levels of the mind and these points
of reference in a constructive, creative manner for all that is
good, honest, pure, clean, and positive. And this is so.
You will continue to strive to take part in constructive and
creative activities to make this a better world to live in,
so that when you move on,
you shall have left behind a better world for those who follow.
You will consider the whole of humanity,
depending on their ages, as fathers or mothers,
brothers or sisters,
sons or daughters.
You are a superior human being.
You have greater understanding.
compassion, and patience with others.
In a moment, I'm going to count from one to five and
cause a sound with my fingers.
At that moment, you will open your eyes, be wide awake, feeling
fine and in perfect health, feeling better than before.
One, two, coming out slowly now.
3.
At the count of 5, you will open your eyes, be wide
awake, feeling fine and in perfect health, feeling better than
before, feeling the way you feel when you have slept the right
amount of revitalizing, refreshing, relaxing, healthy sleep.
4. 5. Eyes open, wide awake, feeling fine and in in perfect
health, feeling better than before.
To guarantee success with your Silva techniques, we recommend
that you take the Silva seminars live. For more information over
course schedules and locations, log on to silvamethod .com or
call 1 -800 -545 -6463 within the continental United States or
956 -722 -6391.
Thank you.